Every morning, my alarm goes off, I wake up from my slumber and hit the snooze button.
每天早上，我的闹钟响起，我从沉睡中醒来，按下贪睡延时按钮。
Then I crawl back under my duvet and catch a few more minutes of shut-eye.
然后我又爬回被子里面，再多睡上几分钟觉。
"I'll go to bed early tonight,"
“今晚我要早点睡觉。”
I tell myself.
我对自己说。
But then, in the evening, I get a second wind and completely forget about my early night.
但是，到了晚上，我又重振雄风，完全忘记了要早睡这件事。
Why am I finding it so difficult to get a good night's sleep?
为什么我觉得睡个好觉这么难呢？
And is it a problem?
这算是个问题吗？
The amount we sleep has declined over the years and insomnia is on the rise.
这些年来我们的睡眠时间减少了，失眠的情况却在增加。
Modern technology is often blamed.
现代科技常常被认为是罪魁祸首。
The light from our smartphone affects levels of melatonin - the sleep-inducing hormone - keeping us wide awake into the early hours.
我们智能手机发出的光会影响褪黑素的水平——褪黑素是一种催眠的激素——让我们一直到凌晨都还十分清醒。
Lack of sleep can seriously damage our health and memory.
睡眠不足会严重影响我们的健康和记忆力。
We need deep sleep to transfer our memories from our short-term storage to our long-term storage.
我们需要深度睡眠来将我们的记忆从短期存储转移到长期存储中。
If we don't sleep enough, we may lose those memories.
如果我们睡眠不足，就可能会失去这些记忆。
This is particularly disastrous for people studying for exams.
这对正在备考的人来说尤其糟糕。
So, how can we learn to sleep better?
那么，我们怎样才能学会更好地睡眠呢？
For Professor Till Roenneberg, it's important people recognise they have an internal body clock.
对于蒂尔·罗内伯格教授来说，重要的是人们要认识到自己有一个内在的生物钟。
This determines whether you are a night owl, an early bird or somewhere in the middle.
这决定了你是一个夜猫子、早起的人，还是介于两者之间。
We don't have any choice.
我们别无选择。
"It's like feet," he said "Some people are born with big feet and some with small feet, but most people are somewhere in the middle."
“这就像脚一样，”他说，“有些人天生脚大，有些人天生脚小，但大多数人都介于两者之间。”
Our work schedules are out of sync with our natural sleep patterns.
我们的工作时间表与我们自然的睡眠模式不同步。
He says this leads to "social jetlag" where people feel like they are constantly in the wrong time zone.
他说这会导致“社交时差”，让人感觉自己总是处于错误的时区。
Paul Kelley - a sleep expert from the University of Oxford - says that most people are getting up too early.
牛津大学的睡眠专家保罗·凯利说，大多数人起床太早了。
He believes work and school should start a few hours later.
他认为工作和上学都应该晚几个小时开始。
Many companies are starting to realise more sleep can mean a more productive workforce and are changing work schedules.
许多公司开始意识到，更多的睡眠意味着更有生产力的劳动力，并且正在改变工作时间表。
While in South Korea, office workers are heading to relaxation parlours at lunchtime to take power naps in hammocks or massage chairs.
而在韩国，上班族会在午餐时间去休闲场所，在吊床或按摩椅上小睡。
This is much healthier than catching forty winks while sitting on the toilet or dropping off at their desks.
这比坐在马桶上打个盹或者在办公桌上睡着要健康得多。
So, if like me you find yourself hitting your snooze button every morning - don't feel bad.
所以，如果你和我一样，发现自己每天早上都在按贪睡按钮，别难过。
It's just our body clocks!
这只是我们的生物钟在作祟！